(Raj:)one should only be...
washing the dishes.
(Howard:)Just because you
have that accent
(Howard:)doesn't mean what
you say isn't stupid.
(Raj:)No, seriously.
(Raj:)It's about being present
in the moment,
(Raj:)focusing on the feeling
of the warm water,
(Raj:)the smell of
the detergent,
(Raj:)the sound of the dishes squeaking,
and following your own breath.
(Raj:)It's about... it's
about simply being.
Ah. (chuckles)
(Howard:)Okay... I'll try it.
(all inhale deeply)
(all exhale)
(Soup Kitchen Manager:)I need three people
out front.
I'll do it!
Me! Right here!
No fair! I was meditating!
(Leonard:)Come on,
don't be mad.
(Leonard:)It was a long time ago,
and it was an accident.
(Penny:)How can reading my journal
be an accident?
(Leonard:)I didn't even
know what it was.
(Leonard:)I saw it on your nightstand.
I picked it up.
(Penny:)Well, when you realized what
it was, why didn't you stop?
(Leonard:)You know me, I'm a
big ol' bookworm.